Guide to the University of Chicago, Yerkes Observatory, Office of the Director Records 1891-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: 1903-1946
  - D-E, 1943, Deutsch, Armin, 5 pages DeVany, Arthur, 2 pages Dictionary of American Biography, 2 pages Dodds, Harold W., 1 page Dornberger, W. W., 2 pages Doty, R. E., 3 pages Dunham, T., 4 pages Durham, Geneva, 4 pages Dushane, G. P., 2 pages Eastman Kodak, 7 pages Ebbighausen, E., 3 pages Edmondson, F., 29 pages Elvey, C. T., 6 pages (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - F, 1943, First National Bank Fath, E. A., 1 page Federer, C. A., 5 pages Fensholt, O. B., 2 pages Fortune, 1 page Fox, Philip, 3 pages (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - G, 1943, Gale, Mrs. H. G., 6 pages Gamow, G., 11 pages Gaposchkin, C. P., 5 pages Gaposchkin, S., 7 pages Garner, Arch, 2 pages Geneva Lake Property Owners, 14 pages Gingrich, C. H., 27 pages Glyptis, Nicholas, 11 pages Goedicke, Victor, 1 page Greenstein, Jesse, 9 pages Guggenheim Foundation, 7 pages (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - H, 1943, Halbach, E. A., 2 pages Hall, R. G., 9 pages Hardinge Brothers, 1 page Harlow, W., 8 pages Harrison, M. H., 2 pages Henrich, L. R., 14 pages Henyey, L. G., 14 pages Herzberg, 86 pages (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - H, 1943, Harvard University Society of Fellows, 1 page Heyden, F. J., 1 page Hiltner, W. A., 67 pages Howell, H. G., 1 page Hoyt, F. C., 6 pages Hujer, Karel, 2 pages Humason, M. L., 2 pages Hynek, J. A., 6 pages (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - I-K, 1943, Iler, G. E., 3 pages Ingalls, A. G., 1 page Ipatieff, V. N., 1 page Jablonski, A., 1 page Janesville Gazette, 3 pages Jardine, Don C., 2 pages Jenkins, L. F., 2 pages Jewett, Frank, 2 pages Jose, Paul D., 1 page Keenan, P. C., 7 pages Kilgore, H. M., 11 pages King, C. A., 3 pages Kingston, H. R., 1 page Klopsteg, Paul E., 1 page Kopff, W. O., 3 pages Kosciuszko Foundation, 16 pages Krogdahl, W. S., 5 pages Kruger, P. G., 2 pages Kuiper, G. P., 74 pages (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - L-M, 1943, Lacroute, P., 1 page Lake Geneva Chamber of Commerce, 1 page Ledoux, Paul, 1 page Lee, O. J., 3 pages Leonard, F. C., 7 pages Lindblad, B., 2 pages Linnel, A., 1 page Lundin, C. A. R., 1 page Lundmark, Knut, 3 pages Luyten, W. J., 10 pages McClellan and Sherman, 4 pages McIlwain, L., 2 pages McKellar, 12 pages McLaughlin, Dean, 14 pages McMath, R. R., 4 pages Marchant, 3 pages Martz, E. P., 1 page Menzel, D. H., 4 pages Microfilms Incorporated, 3 pages Missouri Pacific, 37 pages Mitchell, S. A., 6 pages Moffitt, G. W., 3 pages Monk, G. S., 6 pages Moore, C., 1 page Moore, J. H., 32 pages Morehouse, Mrs. D. W., 1 page Morgan, W. W., 7 pages Mrozowski, S., 9 pages Mulliken, 9 pages Munch, Guido, 33 pages (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - McDonald Observatory, 1943 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - McDonald Observatory, 1943 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - N, 1943, Nassau, J. J., 2 pages National Academy of Sciences, 16 pages National Committee Physicists, 1 page National Decorating Service, 1 page National Defense Research Committee, 6 pages National Research Council, 2 pages Ness, L., 3 pages Neugebauer, O., 3 pages New York Academy of Sciences, 2 pages New York Public Library, 4 pages Neyman, J., 6 pages Nicholson, Seth B., 15 pages Nobel Committee, 1 page Northfield News, 2 pages Northwestern University Library, 3 pages Nowinska, Sylvia, 5 pages (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - O-P, 1943, O’Donnell, Tom, 2 pages Office of Price Administration, 4 pages Oppenheimer, H. D., 1 page Page, Thornton, 9 pages Panofsky, Hans, 3 pages Patterson, Ruth, 4 pages Paul Revere Boys Club, 1 page Pearce, J. A., 2 pages Pearson, Fred, 6 pages Peterson, L. E., 1 page Peterson, W. F., 2 pages Petrie, R. M., 1 page Pettit, E., 2 pages Phillips, J. G., 4 pages Physical Review, 3 pages Pierce, N. L., 1 page Pisani, Emilia, 6 pages Plaskett, H. H., 3 pages Pleasant Hill Academy, 2 pages Pogo, A., 2 pages Polish Institue of Astronomy and Science, 1 page Popper, D. M., 27 pages Popular Astronomy, 1 page Porter, D. R., 4 pages Potwin, L. G., 1 page Prager, R., 1 page Princeton University Observatory, 1 page (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - P, 1943, Papers published Paradox (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Questions, 1943 (Box 209, Folder 5-6)
  - R, 1943, Reprint requests Rainey, H. D., 6 pages Randers, G., 11 pages Ration Board, 3 pages Reuyl, D., 1 page Rezek, C. L., 2 pages Ridell, C., 6 pages Ringstad, J., 1 page Robinson, L. V., 2 pages Rodriguez, J., 1 page Ross, F. E., 4 pages Royal Astronomical Society, 3 pages Royal Typewriter, 1 page Rudnick, Paul, 2 pages Rufus, W. C., 2 pages Russell, H. N., 8 pages Rust, Carl, 2 pages (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - S, 1943, Sanford, Roscoe F., 14 pages Scheiby, E., 1 page Schein, M., 6 pages Schenberg, M., 6 pages Schlesinger, F., 2 pages Science, 3 pages Science Service, 4 pages Scientific American, 1 page Seely, Warner, 10 pages Selective Service, 13 pages Sen, H. K., 1 page Shane, C. D., 3 pages Sharpless, S. L., 4 pages Shaw, R. W., 2 pages Sheek, E. L., 1 page Sigma Xi, 7 pages Simmons, C. D. (Univeristy of Texas), 19 pages Sitterly, C. M., 3 pages Slocum, F., 3 pages A. O. Smith, 3 pages Smith, Burke, 16 pages Southern Methodist University, 2 pages Spitzer, L., 17 pages Stebbins, Joel, 5 pages Steel, Helen, 19 pages Sterne, T. E., 5 pages Stevenson, John, 2 pages Stilwell, C. J., 4 pages Sullivan, F., 1 page Swensson, J. W., 4 pages Switzerland Legation Wider Kehr, 6 pages (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - S, 1943, Shapley, 64 pages Swings, 64 pages (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - S-T, 1943, Spectrograph CID Tallmadge, G. K., 2 pages Thackeray, A. D., 1 page Tilley, E. C., 10 pages Time Magazine, 2 pages Titus, John, 25 pages Triplett Electrical, 2 pages (Box 210, Folder 2)
  - U-V, 1943, Uhler, H. S., 2 pages United Nations in America, 3 pages United States Civil Service Commission, 7 pages United States Senate, 4 pages USSR Society for Cultural Relations, 1 page Visitors, Tai, Osterbrock (Box 210, Folder 3)
  - V, 1943, Valverde, R. R., 1 page Van Biesbroeck, G., 48 pages Van Biesbroeck, M., 1 page Van de Kamp, Peter, 3 pages Van Dyke, Suzanne, 3 pages Vard, Incorporated, 6 pages Vosatka, J., 7 pages Vyssotsky, A. N., 4 pages (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - W-Z, 1943, Walters, R., 2 pages Weaver, H. F., 11 pages Weaver, Warren, 6 pages Wells, H. B., 1 page White House (El Paso), 2 pages Whitt, S. S., 5 pages Wight, E., 1 page Wilkens, A., 1 page Williams, Marjorie, 4 pages Williams, W. L., 2 pages Williams Bay Budget, 1 page Williamson, Raphy E., 19 pages Wilson, P. B., 2 pages Wisconsin Adademy of Arts and Sciences, 3 pages Wisconsin Power and Light, 2 pages Wisconsin Telephone, 7 pages Wright, W. H., 1 page Wyse, Mrs. A. B., 2 pages Yale University, 4 pages Yowell, E. I., 1 page Zachariasen, W. H., 2 pages (Box 210, Folder 5)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds (Box 210, Folder 6)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, electric bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid (Box 210, Folder 7)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements (Box 210, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago Bursar, 1943 (Box 210, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago Business Manager, 1943 (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes petty cash University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald petty cash (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, 1943 (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Divisional Office, 1943 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago, Filbey University of Chicago, Bartkey (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago fellowship applications University of Chicago Library Univeristy of Chicago University of Chicago notices (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago President’s Office University of Chicago Hutchins (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1943 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago Press University of Chicago Photo Department Univeristy of Chicago Publicity (Box 212, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Purchasing Agent, 1943 (Box 212, Folder 2)
  - U, 1943, Univeristy of Chicago Registrar University of Chicago colloquia University of Chicago observing program University of Chicago reports (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - U, 1943, University of Chicago Personnel University of Chicago acquisitions (Box 212, Folder 4)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Mary Alexander, 1944 (Box 212, Folder 5)
  - A, 1944, Astrophysical Journal, Merrill Astrophysical Journal, finances Astrophysical Journal, subscription reports (Box 212, Folder 6)
  - A, 1944, Astrophysical Journal Applications for positions (Box 212, Folder 7)
  - A, 1944, Aluminizing chamber Airport project Adams, C. H., 5 pages Adams, W. S., 10 pages Adler Planetarium, 1 page Airy, Anna, 3 pages Aitken, R. F., 2 pages Alien Property Office, 3 pages Alton Railroad, 1 page American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 8 pages American Association Advancement of Science, 1 page American Astronomical Society, 11 pages American Philosophical Society, 5 pages American Physical Society, 5 pages Areson, Clinton W., 2 pages T. L. Artz Foundry, 1 page Aurora College, 4 pages Avakian, Emil, 3 pages (Box 212, Folder 8)
  - B, 1944, Baade, W., 8 pages Babcock, H. W., 1 page Bailey, D. K., 3 pages Bailey, F. S., 2 pages Baker, R. H., 2 pages Bauer, C. A., 26 pages Beals, C. S., 5 pages Beck, Guido, 3 pages Bedell, A. L., 2 pages Belland, F. R., 8 pages Beloit College, 2 pages Bentsen, H. B., 2 pages Bidelman, W., 4 pages Bishop Post Card Company, 2 pages Blakiston Company, 6 pages Blanco, Victor, 3 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 6 pages Bok, B., 52 pages Bowen, I. S., 2 pages Bowerman, W. G., 2 pages Briscoe, H. T., 2 pages Brouwer, Dirk, 25 pages Buchta, J. W., 2 pages Burns, Keivin, 6 pages Butler, U., 2 pages Buttrick, J. F., 1 page (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - C, 1944, Cooperative Project Calhoun, J. W., 3 pages University of California Library, 1 page Calvert, M. C., 5 pages Campbell, Leon, 2 pages Carlson, Martha, 1 page Carpenter, A. H., 6 pages Carter Observatory, 1 page Cesco, Carlos, 13 pages Chalonge, D., 2 pages Chandrasekhar, S., 21 pages Chang, Y. C., 4 pages Chicago and Alton Railroad, 1 page Collins, O. C., 9 pages Cornell, H. W., 6 pages Corning Glass Works, 2 pages Crawford, R. T., 2 pages Cuffey, James, 5 pages (Box 213, Folder 2)
  - D, 194, Dempster, A. J., 2 pages Denmark (Book Project), 9 pages Dershem, Elmer, 2 pages Deutsch, A., 6 pages Dirks, W. H., 2 pages Distillation Products Company, 1 page Dornberger, W. W., 2 pages Douglas, A. V., 3 pages Dover Publications, 3 pages Drummond Lorena (University of Texas), 5 pages Duncan, John C., 3 pages Dunham, T., 1 page Dunn, L. C., 13 pages Durham, Geneva, 1 page Dwyer, R. J., 8 pages (Box 213, Folder 3)
  - E, 1944, Eastman Kodak, 15 pages Ebbighausen, E., 8 pages Eddington, A. S., 11 pages Edmondson, Frank, 36 pages Elbert, W. J., 2 pages Elvey, C. T., 3 pages Encyclopedia Britannica, 7 pages Erro, L. E., 7 pages (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - F, 1944, First National Bank Fath, E. A., 2 pages Fechtenburg, J. F., 1 page Federer, C. A., 10 pages Fortune, 1 page Fraenkel, C. Peter, 1 page Franklin Institute, 1 page (Box 213, Folder 5)
  - G, 1944, Gaertner, W., 5 pages Gallo, J., 2 pages Gamow, G., 15 pages Gaposchkin, C. P., 38 pages Gaposchkin, S., 18 pages Gaviola, E., 2 pages General Electric Company, 5 pages General Motors, 2 pages Geneva Lake Property Owners Association, 12 pages Thomas B. Gibbs Company, 1 page Gilkey, Charles W., 2 pages Gingrich, C. H., 8 pages Gleissberg, W., 4 pages Goedicke, V., 3 pages Greenstein, Jesse L., 5 pages Guggenheim Foundation, 16 pages (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - Herzberg, G., 76 pages (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - H, 1944, Hall, R. G., 3 pages Hansen, Julie M. Vinter, 2 pages Henrich, L. R., 3 pages Henroteau, F., 5 pages Henyey, L. G., 4 pages Herbig, G. H., 4 pages Herriott, W., 3 pages Heyden, F. J., 6 pages Hiltner, W. A., 96 pages Hoover, Blaine, 7 pages Hopkins, Richard, 2 pages Howorka, H., 1 page Hoyt, F. C., 7 pages Hubbard, S. E., 6 pages Huffer, R., 1 page Hunter, A. S., 1 page Hynek, J. A., 11 pages (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - I-K, 1944, India Calcutta University, 1 page Jenkins, Louise F., 3 pages Johnson, Alice, 1 page Jones, H. Spencer, 3 pages Jose, Paul D., 1 page Joy, A. H., 2 pages Kaempffert, W., 1 page Keenan, P. C., 12 pages Keith, L. J. (Follett), 4 pages Kinnaird, R. F., 3 pages Kopal, Z., 12 pages Kopff, William O., 7 pages Koscuiszko Foundation, 2 pages Kreider, H. R., 4 pages Krogdahl, W. S., 6 pages Krogman, L. W., 1 page Kuiper, G. P., 44 pages Kuiper, Sarah, 31 pages (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - L-M, 1944, Laves, Kurt, 3 pages Laing, Gordon J., 4 pages Lee, O. J., 7 pages Lemon, H. B., 2 pages Lunde, E., 12 pages Luyten, W. J., 40 pages McCorkle, G. C., 1 page McKellar, A., 4 pages McLaughlin, D. B., 11 pages McMath, R. R., 2 pages (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - McDonald Observatory, 1944 (Box 214, Folder 3-4)
  - M, 1944, Malin, M. F., 4 pages Manganiello, V., 5 pages Marchant, 5 pages Marshall, Roy K., 5 pages Martin, Monroe H., 11 pages Martinoff, D., 3 pages Menzel, D. H., 11 pages Microfilms, Incorporated, 2 pages Milne, E. A., 7 pages Minerva Booksellers, 2 pages Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 2 pages Milwaukee School Board, 5 pages Missouri Pacific Lines, 61 pages (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - M, 1944, Mitchell, S. A., 14 pages Mokrzycki, G. A., 8 pages Monk, G. S., 2 pages Monnig, O. E., 4 pages Monthly Evening Sky Map, 1 page Moore, J. H., 23 pages Morelock, H. W., 4 pages Morgan, W. W., 3 pages Motor Transport, 1 page Moulton, F. R., 4 pages Mulliken, R. S., 7 pages Munch, Guido, 35 pages (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - Morgan Monograph, 1940-1944 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - N-O, 1944, Nakhatovitsch, D. I., 1 page Nassau, J. J., 3 pages National Academy of Sciences, 5 pages National Bureau of Standards, 2 pages National Research Council, 3 pages Nautical Almanac Office, 7 pages Nef, John N., 5 pages Neville, Maude, 3 pages New York Academy of Sciences, 1 page Neyman, J., 1 page Nicholson, S. B., 8 pages Northwestern University Library, 1 page Observatory, 9 pages O’Keefe, John, 5 pages Oppenheimer, H. D., 7 pages (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Optical Department, 1943-1944 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - P, 1944, Page, T. L., 2 pages Palmer, P. S., 2 pages Parkinson, W. C., 4 pages Patterson, Ruth, 8 pages Pawlowski, F. W., 2 pages Payne, F., 3 pages Pearce, J. A., 1 page Pearson, Carlton, 6 pages Peterson, Mildred, 1 page Petrie, W., 4 pages Pettit, Edison, 2 pages Phillips, J. G., 2 pages Phillips, Oliver, 2 pages Planetarium, Adler, newspaper clippings Pleasant Hill Academy, 1 page Popper, D. M., 11 pages Prager, Richard, 4 pages Pringshelm, Peter, 1 page Pullman Company, 1 page Papers published Paradox (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - Questions, 1944 (Box 215, Folder 4-5)
  - R, 1944, Radcliffe College, 1 page Rainey, H. P. (including newspaper clippings), 21 pages Randers, Gunnar, 2 pages Rationing Board, 1 page Reber, Grote, 9 pages Recillas, P. P., 2 pages Reuling, J. A., 1 page Richardson, R. S., 1 page Riddle, J. P., 3 pages Ridell, Charles, 6 pages Ringstad, J., 2 pages Rodriguez, Joe, 4 pages Royal Astronomical Society, 6 pages Russell, H. N., 24 pages Russian War Relief, 3 pages (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - Shapley, 67 pages, 1944 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - S, 1944, Saha, M. N., 3 pages Sahade, J., 17 pages Sandage, A. R., 2 pages Schein, Marcel, 4 pages Schenberg, M., 6 pages Scherer, R., 2 pages Schilt, J., 1 page Schlesinger, W., 1 page Science, 5 pages Science Service, 2 pages Seares, F. H., 4 pages Seely, Warner, 6 pages Selective Services, 5 pages Sen, H. K., 1 page Sen, N. R., 9 pages Shallenberger, M., 2 pages Shane, C. D., 2 pages Sharpless, S. L., 9 pages Shaw, R. W., 3 pages Shneiderov, A. J., 2 pages Sigma Xi, 7 pages Simmons, C. D., 9 pages Slettebek, A. E., 3 pages Smith, Burke, 43 pages Smith, A. O., 1 page Spitzer, L., 10 pages Stahr, M. E., 5 pages (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - S, 1944, Star Engraving, 2 pages Stark, J. H. L., 1 page Statler Hotel, Boston, 2 pages Stebbins, Joel, 8 pages Steel, Helen, 12 pages Stewart, J. Q., 2 pages Stilwell, C. J., 2 pages Stolfa, L., 3 pages Stonyhurst College Observatory, 1 page Stromgren, 1 page Sun (Chicago), 1 page Swensson, J. W., 1 page Swings, P., 89 pages Sydney Observatory, 1 page (Box 216, Folder 2)
  - T-V, 1944, Taylor, Philip H., 7 pages Thomas, Merle, 1 page Tilley, T. C., 1 page Titus, John, 9 pages Tree Tool and Die, 6 pages Underhill, A. B., 2 pages United Airlines, 2 pages United Educators, 11 pages United States Naval Observatory, 1 page United States Post Office, 2 pages USSR Society Cultural Relations, 2 pages Van Biesbroeck, G., 46 pages Van Biesbroeck, Julia, 2 pages Van de Kamp, P., 3 pages Van den Bos, W. H., 2 pages Van Dijke, Suzanne E. A., 7 pages Van Houten, F. K., 3 pages Vyssoksky, A. N., 5 pages (Box 216, Folder 3)
  - Visitors, 1944 (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - W-Z, 1944, Wagman, N. E., 7 pages Wares, Gordon, 40 pages Weaver, H. F., 10 pages Who’s Who, 1 page Whyburn, G. T., 8 pages Wickham, Mrs. Roy, 1 page Wilkens, A., 3 pages Williams, R. C., 12 pages Williamson, Ralph, 10 pages Willis, H. L., 5 pages Wisconsin Academy of Sciences, 2 pages Wisconsin Power and Light, 1 page Wisconsin Southern Gas, 1 page Wisconsin Telephone Company, 3 pages Wood, R. W., 9 pages Wright, C. O., 13 pages Wright, W. H., 2 pages Wulf, O., 2 pages Wylie, C. C., 3 pages Yale University Observatory, 1 page Zachariassen, W., 2 pages (Box 216, Folder 5)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago Bookstore University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds (Box 216, Folder 6)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, electric bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, statements (Box 216, Folder 7)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, bills paid University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, orders (Box 216, Folder 8)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago Bursar University of Chicago Business Manager (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, 1944 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald petty cash University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald payroll University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes petty cash University of Chicago Comptroller, Yerkes payroll (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago Comptroller, McDonald bills paid, 1944 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago Division Dean University of Chicago Division (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago fellowship applications University of Chicago Library University of Chicago (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago notices University of Chicago President University of Chicago Filbey University of Chicago President’s Office University of Chicago Hutchins (Box 217, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1944 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Publicity, 1944 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago Purchasing Agent, 1944 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago Registrar University of Chicago colloquia University of Chicago reports University of Chicago personnel (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - U, 1944, University of Chicago observing program University of Chicago requisitions (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Astrophysical Journal, reprint orders, 1945 (Box 218, Folder 6)
  - Applications for positions, 1945 (Box 218, Folder 7)
  - A, 1945, Abbot, C. G., 2 pages Abetti, G., 5 pages Adams, C. A. (Astronomical Society Pacific), 4 pages Adams, W. S., 48 pages Adel, Arthur, 4 pages Aitken, R. G., 1 page Allen, L. H., 18 pages Alumni Bulletin, 1 page American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 5 pages American Association Advancement Science, 4 pages American Astronomical Society, 3 pages American Institute of Physics, 7 pages American Journal of Physics, 3 pages American Philosophical Society, 6 pages American Physics Society, 1 page Annear, Paul, 1 page Atlas Press Company, 2 pages (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - B, 1945, Babcock, H. W., 3 pages Bailey, E. M., 9 pages Bailland, J., 1 page Baker, James G., 2 pages Baker, R. H., 4 pages Bakhmeteff (Bush Report), 10 pages Balfe, Mrs. J., 1 page Ball, John Jr., 3 pages Benerji, A. C., 1 page Barbier, D., 1 page Barker, E. F., 2 pages Bauer, C. A., 6 pages Bauer, Grace M., 2 pages Bausch and Lomb, 13 pages Beals, C. S., 3 pages Belgium (Louvain University Library), 1 page Observatory Royale de Belgique, 1 page Beloit College, 2 pages Beloit Typewriter, 1 page Benjamin Hotel, 1 page Bennot, M., 1 page Bentsen, H. B., 1 page Bernstein, H. J., 1 page Bidelman, W. P., 10 pages Birge, R. T., 1 page Blaauw, A., 2 pages Blakiston Company, 2 pages Blanco, Victor, 4 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T., 11 pages (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - B, 1945, Bodine Electric, 2 pages Bok, B. J., 27 pages Bowen, I. S., 2 pages Brasch, F. E., 6 pages Encyclopaedia Britannica, 4 pages Brouwer, Dirk, 1 page Broyles, A. A., 9 pages Buchta, J. W., 3 pages Burke, Ralph, 1 page Burke and James, 1 page Burns, Keivin, 2 pages (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Cooperative project, 1945 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - C, 1945, Calhoun, J. W., 8 pages Calvert, M. R., 4 pages Cambridge University, 1 page Carlson, O., 1 page Carlson Planetarium, 1 page Carlson, Wilfred, 1 page Carnegie Institute, 2 pages Carpenter, A. H., 7 pages Cattell, Ware, 10 pages Cesco, C. U., 11 pages Chalonge, D., 11 pages Chamberlin, R. T., 3 pages Chance Brothers, 1 page Chandrasekhar, S., 15 pages Change, Y. C., 4 pages Chant, C. A., 1 page Chiang, Fu-Tsung, 2 pages Chicago Apparatus Company, 1 page Chile, S. Salvo (see paradox), 1 page Code, A. D., 2 pages Compton, A. H., 8 pages Conant, J. B., 2 pages Conwell, E., 10 pages Cornell, H. W., 2 pages Coronet Magazine, 5 pages Cowling, T. G., 1 page Crew, H., 1 page Cunningham, L. E., 5 pages (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - D, 1945, Delporte, E., 4 pages Dempster, A. J., 3 pages Deutsch, A., 12 pages Dirks, W. H., 1 page Distillation Products, 1 page Dodson, Helen W., 4 pages Dornberger, W. W., 1 page Dorsey, N. E., 3 pages Douglas, A. V., 2 pages Douglas, J., 4 pages Dover Publications, 6 pages Drummond, Lorena, 2 pages Dunham, R. J., 3 pages Dunham, T., 6 pages Eclipse (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - E, 1945, Eastman Kodak, 31 pages Ebbighauser, E. G., 5 pages Eddington, W., 2 pages Edmondson, F. K., 63 pages C. F. Elmes Engineering Works, 2 pages Encyclopaedia Britannica, 42 pages Erro, L. E., 5 pages (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - F, 1945, Federer, C. A., Jr., 8 pages Fensholt, O. B., 2 pages Filbey, E. T., 1 page Fisher, Clyde, 5 pages Franck, J., 1 page Franklin Institute, 2 pages Freeman, I. M., 2 pages Freundlich, E. F., 2 pages Frost, Mrs. E. B., 2 pages First National Bank (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - G, 1945, Gaertner Scientific Corporation, 8 pages Gallo, J., 1 page Gamow, G., 8 pages Gaposchkin, Cecilia P., 13 pages Gaposchkin, Sergei, 7 pages Gaviola, E., 9 pages General Electric Company, 2 pages Geneva Lake Property Owners Association, 11 pages Giclas, H. L., 1 page Gill, Jocelyn R., 1 page Gingrich, C. H., 16 pages Ginn and Company, 2 pages Gleissberg, W., 1 page Glyptis, N., 1 page Goucher College, 1 page Greece Astronomical Observatory, 1 page Green, L. C., 2 pages Greenstein, Jesse L., 11 pages Grolier Encyclopedia, 3 pages Gruslin, R., 1 page Guggenheim Foundation, 12 pages (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - H, 1945, Halbach, E. A., 1 page Hancock, Frank, 23 pages Harrison, M. H., 3 pages Hayden Planetarium, 2 pages Henyey, L. G., 15 pages Herrick, S., 5 pages Hertzsprung, E., 2 pages Herzberg, G., 58 pages Heyden, F. J., 5 pages Adam Hilger Limited, 2 pages (Box 220, Folder 1)